=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 16=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 16 =
Dear, we're about to reach the capital.
عزيزي ، نحن على وشك الوصول إلى العاصمة.
It must be tiring for you.
يجب أن يكون متعبًا بالنسبة لك.
Your belonging!
الانتماء الخاص بك!
That person is weird.
هذا الشخص غريب.
Be careful!
كن حذرا!
I'm the constable's daughter.
أنا ابنة الشرطي.
Do you think that you can bully us easily?
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنك التنمر علينا بسهولة؟
You lowly servant,
أيها العبد المتواضع ،
how dare you attack me?
كيف تجرؤ على مهاجمتي؟
Go take her down
اذهب وانزلها
and send her to the court.
وإرسالها إلى المحكمة.
Hold on. What about you who attacked me first?
يتمسك.  ماذا عنك الذي هاجمني أولا؟
(Qi Jingyu)
(تشي جينغيو)
I just wanted to see if you can protect my sister
أردت فقط معرفة ما إذا كان بإمكانك حماية أختي
or not as my brother-in-law.
أو ليس شقيق زوجتي.
Brother-in-law?
شقيق الزوج؟
Come on, Chu Yuzhi.
تعال ، تشو يوجي.
Have you forgotten about me?
هل نسيتني؟
I'm Qi Jingyu.
أنا Qi Jingyu.
Although we last met...
على الرغم من أننا التقينا آخر مرة ...
Although we last met 10 years ago,
على الرغم من أننا التقينا آخر مرة منذ 10 سنوات ،
I remember the jade that
أتذكر ذلك اليشم
you're wearing.
كنت ترتدي.
This is the gift my father gave to my future brother-in-law.
هذه هي الهدية التي قدمها والدي إلى زوج أختي المستقبلي.
Qi...
تشي ...
Qi Jingyu?
تشى جينغيو؟
I remember now.
أتذكر الآن.
You're the useless young master that didn't get to pass
أنت السيد الشاب عديم الفائدة الذي لم ينجح
the imperial examination for eight times.
الامتحان الامبراطوري ثماني مرات.
I have yet to take my eighth examination.
لا يزال يتعين علي إجراء امتحاني الثامن.
How dare you.
كيف تجرؤ.
You beat me up and cursed me?
لقد ضربتني وسبتني؟
Mr. Qi,
السيد تشي ،
even if she's a servant,
حتى لو كانت خادمة ،
she's my family's servant.
إنها خادمة عائلتي.
Mr. Qi, are you trying to show off your power
السيد تشي ، هل تحاول التباهي بقوتك
as soon as we met?
حالما التقينا؟
Since my brother-in-law is speaking for you,
بما أن شقيق زوجي يتحدث نيابة عنك ،
I'll just let this slide
سأترك هذه الشريحة فقط
and let you go.
واتركك تذهب.
Quickly come back with me.
بسرعة عد معي.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Dear,
عزيزي،
why did you say that you're Mr. Chu?
لماذا قلت إنك السيد تشو؟
Mr. Qi is arrogant
السيد تشي متعجرف
and revengeful.
والانتقام.
If I told him that I'm not Chu Yuzhi,
إذا أخبرته أنني لست تشو يوجي ،
he will not go easy on you.
لن يتساهل عليك.
(Grand Chancellor's Residence)
(سكن المستشار الكبير)
Father.
(منزل المستشار الكبير) الأب.
Look who I've brought here.
انظر من جئت إلى هنا.
(Grand Chancellor Qi) Mr. Chu Yuzhi.
(المستشار الكبير تشي) السيد تشو يوجي.
We have a guest.
لدينا ضيف.
Greetings, Grand Chancellor.
تحية طيبة ، المستشار الأكبر.
Don't call me that.
لا تدعوني بهذا.
Call me father-in-law.
اتصل بي والد زوجتك.
After more than 10 years,
بعد أكثر من 10 سنوات ،
you've become more handsome.
لقد أصبحت أكثر وسامة.
You're indeed General Chu's son.
أنت بالفعل ابن الجنرال تشو.
Father asked me to send his regards.
طلب مني أبي أن أرسل تحياته.
Okay, I've discussed with your father.
حسنًا ، لقد ناقشت مع والدك.
We'll both hold the wedding banquet.
كلانا سنعقد مأدبة الزفاف.
We'll hold it here first.
سنعقده هنا أولاً.
Quickly get Qiaoyan here
احصل بسرعة على Qiaoyan هنا
to meet her fiance.
لمقابلة خطيبها.
Father,
أب،
I'll go back first.
سأعود أولا.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Come and have a seat.
تعال واجلس.
You lowly servant,
أيها العبد المتواضع ،
why are you still standing here?
لماذا مازلت واقفا هنا
We don't have enough servants.
ليس لدينا عدد كاف من الخدم.
Go and help out.
اذهب وساعد.
Madam Zhang.
سيدتي تشانغ.
(Madam Zhang) Mr. Qi.
(سيدتي تشانغ) السيد تشي.
Get something
احصل على شيء
for her to work on.
لها للعمل عليها.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Go!
يذهب!
I'm Mr. Chu's servant.
أنا خادم السيد تشو.
I can't do this.
لا استطيع فعل هذا.
Stop mumbling.
توقف عن الغمغمة.
You have to follow our rules
عليك أن تتبع قواعدنا
in the Grand Chancellor's residence.
في مقر إقامة المستشار الأكبر.
Brush it now.
نظفها الآن.
Dear, you must be tired.
عزيزي ، لابد أنك متعب.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪